Contact

chetans2006@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Requirements Analysis · SDLC
· Java · Testing · Selenium
WebDriver · STLC · Japanese
coordination · Regression Testing
· Agile Methodologies

Accomplishments · See all

2 Languages · 1 Certification

Chetan Rao

Team Lead - Japanese Coordination Support team at Sony Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

A total of 5+ years of experience in Japanese language support and all major administrative tasks• Currently looking for a position in an organization where my Administrative management skills and/or Japanese language skills can be utilized to the best of my abilities.

Experience

Team Lead - Japanese Support team · Sony

July 2010 - Present · Bangalore

Roles & Responsibilities: •Bilingual Japanese coordination support•Act as first point of contact for employees on Admin related activities.•Manage the infrastructure, Liaison with building authority to complete of all facility related issues. •Manage employee transport & ensure proper routing of the cabs to re

Bilingual Japanese coordinator · IBM India Pvt Ltd.

July 2009 - June 2010 (1 year)

Bilingual Software test engineer · Nichi-In Software Solutions Pvt. Ltd. July 2007 - April 2009 (1 year 10 months)

Education

Jyothy Kendriya Vidyalaya, Bangalore

